freepornday.com 2016-11-16

# Free Porn Day | Privacy Policy

Effective 22 August 2016

Gamma Entertainment Inc. and Echo Alpha Inc are providing the services of FreePornDay and together they shall be known as "We", "Us" and "Our". We understand that the privacy of FreePornDay Users (You) is very important. During the navigation of the Portal (www.freepornday.com) certain non-personally identifiable information about Users is collected and Users may submit some personally identifiable information; therefore We have developed this policy to inform You about the collection and use of such information.

### What is Collected

By navigating the site We collect information such as but not limited browser type, country of origin, time of visit (i.e. metadata). By communicating with Us at info@freepornday.com Users may submit personally identifiable information such as email, name or contact information; and this information is also collected by Us.

### Consent

Users agreed to receive email communication regarding the FreePornDay event when they entered their email address and validated their address by confirming receipt of an email from td3x.com.

In order to continue using the Portal, Users must accept certain cookies while browsing the Portal or accessing third party websites via the Portal. Should Users wish to remove cookies or not enable their use, Users may not have access to all areas or services of the Portal

### Security

We take reasonable precautions against external threats to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about Users, and to protect against the loss, misuse and alterations of information under Our control. Any personally identifiable information held by Gamma Entertainment Inc is stored in a secure location (behind a firewall with limited administrative access).

### How Information is Used

Metadata is used to ensure services We provide are accurate, available and working as We believe Users expect. Any personally identifiable information allows Us to process requests and enforce any agreements or terms.

Users may submit metadata and/or personally identifiable information to third-party web service providers from whom We purchase services. Users should read the privacy policy of those third parties whenever possible.

Users may be contacted via email after the FreePornDay event to ask for their opinion about the event, ask for permission to send promotional emails, or to provide additional information regarding FreePornDay. All emails from Gamma Entertainment Inc will include simple instructions on how to unsubscribe and this may be done at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email. Your email address will be removed from the list within 48 hours. Users may NOT opt out of receiving emails regarding account details such as responses to questions.

### Sharing Information With Third Parties

We may disclose metadata information collected with the third party websites participating in the FreePornDay event, if required by law, court order or other governmental authority. Any personally identifiable information may be disclosed if required by law, court order or other governmental authority or when We believe in good faith that disclosing this information is otherwise necessary or advisable, including to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing Us injury or interfering with Our rights or property.

In the event of a change of ownership (merger, acquisition, sale of assets) both Echo Alpha Inc and Gamma Entertainment Inc independently reserve the right to transfer all User information collected, transferred to and used by Us to such separate entity.

### Legal

Users have the right to access personal information We collect and request this information be corrected in case of discrepancies. Personally identifiable information collected is stored and processed in Canada. By choosing to continue to receive communications from Us, Users consent to any transfer of such information outside the country in which they reside or access the Portal and to be bound by the laws of Canada.

This policy does not apply to any linked websites to Us. Please consult the privacy policy and terms and conditions of the website to which redirection may occur if clicking on any banner or advertisement.

By using/navigating the Portal, Users acknowledge they have read, understood and agree to be bound by this privacy policy. Headings are for ease of reference only.
